{"food":[{"level":"1","type":"food","question":"I am yellow and you peel me before you eat me. Monkeys love me! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💛 I am the color of the sun."},{"text":"🐒 Monkeys like to eat me."},{"text":"➡️ You take off my jacket before you eat me."}],"options":[{"label":"Apple","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Banana","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Orange","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"2","type":"food","question":"I am white and I'm good in cereal. Cows give me to you. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I am a liquid."},{"text":"🐄 You get me from an animal."},{"text":"🥣 I taste yummy with cereal."}],"options":[{"label":"Juice","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Milk","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Water","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"3","type":"food","question":"I am orange and crunchy. Rabbits like to eat me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 I grow in the ground."},{"text":"🐰 Bunnies love me!"},{"text":"🧡 My color is like a sunset."}],"options":[{"label":"Carrot","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tomato","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Potato","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"4","type":"food","question":"I am round and red. I grow on trees and keep the doctor away. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌳 I grow on a tree."},{"text":"🍎 My skin is red."},{"text":"🩺 They say one a day keeps the doctor away!"}],"options":[{"label":"Cherry","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Apple","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Strawberry","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"5","type":"food","question":"I am long and green. You can eat me raw or cooked. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥬 I am a vegetable."},{"text":"🐍 I am long like a snake."},{"text":"🥗 I am good in salads."}],"options":[{"label":"Broccoli","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cucumber","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Lettuce","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"6","type":"food","question":"I am round and can be green, red, or purple. I grow in bunches on a vine. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍇 I grow in a cluster."},{"text":"🍷 Juice can be made from me."},{"text":"🌱 I grow on vines."}],"options":[{"label":"Grapes","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Blueberries","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cherries","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"7","type":"food","question":"I am yellow, you can spread me on bread, and bees make me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍞 I taste good on toast."},{"text":"🐝 Bees make me!"},{"text":"🍯 I am sweet and sticky."}],"options":[{"label":"Butter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Honey","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Jam","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"8","type":"food","question":"I am a vegetable that makes you cry when you cut me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧅 I am round and papery."},{"text":"😢 I make you cry!"},{"text":"🍔 I taste good on a burger."}],"options":[{"label":"Garlic","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Onion","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Ginger","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"9","type":"food","question":"I am made from milk, but I am hard. You can slice me or grate me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧀 I'm often yellow or white."},{"text":"🐭 Mice like me!"},{"text":"🍕 I taste yummy on pizza."}],"options":[{"label":"Yogurt","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cheese","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cream","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"10","type":"food","question":"I am made of flour, water, and yeast, and baked in an oven. I come in many shapes and sizes. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥖 You can make a sandwich with me."},{"text":"🔥 I need to be baked."},{"text":"🌾 I am made with flour."}],"options":[{"label":"Cake","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bread","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cookie","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}}],"transport":[{"level":"1","type":"transport","question":"I have wheels and go 'vroom vroom!' What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚗 Grown-ups drive me!"},{"text":"🚦 I stop at red lights."},{"text":"👪 I can carry your family."}],"options":[{"label":"Car","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Boat","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","color":"blue"}},{"level":"2","type":"transport","question":"I float on the water. Chugga chugga!","hints":[{"text":"🌊 I need a big ocean or lake."},{"text":"⚓ I have an anchor."},{"text":"🚢 You can ride me to far away places."}],"options":[{"label":"Train","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Boat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bike","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","color":"blue"}},{"level":"3","type":"transport","question":"I fly in the sky and take people on trips.","hints":[{"text":"☁️ I go very high."},{"text":"💺 I have seats inside."},{"text":"✈️ I have wings."}],"options":[{"label":"Rocket","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bus","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","color":"blue"}},{"level":"4","type":"transport","question":"I go on tracks and carry many people.","hints":[{"text":"🛤️ I follow a special path."},{"text":"📢 You might hear a loud whistle."},{"text":" 🚝 I can be very long."}],"options":[{"label":"Train","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Scooter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Helicopter","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","color":"blue"}},{"level":"5","type":"transport","question":"I have two wheels and you pedal me.","hints":[{"text":" ➦ You can ride me in the park."},{"text":" 🚴 I have handlebars to steer."},{"text":" 🔔 I might have a bell."}],"options":[{"label":"Car","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bike","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Truck","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","color":"blue"}},{"level":"6","type":"transport","question":"I take lots of kids to school and am usually yellow.","hints":[{"text":" 🚦 I have a stop sign that comes out."},{"text":" 🎒 I have lots of seats."},{"text":" 🏫 The driver takes you to and from school."}],"options":[{"label":"Taxi","isCorrect":false},{"label":"School Bus","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Van","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","color":"blue"}},{"level":"7","type":"transport","question":"I'm a truck that helps put out fires.","hints":[{"text":"🚒 I'm bright red."},{"text":"🚨 I have a loud siren."},{"text":"💧 I spray water to stop the fire."}],"options":[{"label":"Garbage Truck","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Fire Truck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Ice Cream Truck","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","color":"blue"}},{"level":"8","type":"transport","question":"I travel to outer space.","hints":[{"text":"👨‍🚀 Astronauts use me."},{"text":"🪐 I explore the solar system."},{"text":"🚀 I have a powerful engine."}],"options":[{"label":"Submarine","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rocket","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tractor","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","color":"blue"}},{"level":"9","type":"transport","question":"I am a vehicle that can go on land and in the water.","hints":[{"text":" 🦆 I am often used by the military"},{"text":" 🛢️I float and have wheels!"},{"text":" 🚧 I can drive onto land and enter the water from land."}],"options":[{"label":"Amphibious Vehicle","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Hovercraft","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Monster Truck","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","color":"blue"}},{"level":"10","type":"transport","question":"I can fly but I don’t have wings and my blades spin very fast","hints":[{"text":"🚁 I can hover in one place."},{"text":"🚑 I am used as an air ambulance."},{"text":"🚦 I can land on the top of buildings."}],"options":[{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Helicopter","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Blimp","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","color":"blue"}}]}